WSYR Collection
WSYR Collection
- Audiorecordings
  - Charles Kettering, part 3; E. R. Vadeboncoeur and WSYR radio news, 04/27/1949; 05/07/1949; wsyr_radio_004; opening of the Thompson Road Campus Science and Engineering.; Lacquer discs/acetates
    Side 1: "Charles Kettering", Part III; Side 2: "E. R. Vadeboncoeur, WSYR radio news", 05/07/1949
  - Charles Kettering, parts 1 and 5, 04/27/1949; wsyr_radio_002; opening of the Thompson Road Campus Science and Engineering - College of Applied Science; Lacquer discs/acetates
    Side 1: "Charles Kettering", Part I; Side 2: "Charles Kettering", Part V
  - Charles Kettering, parts 2 and 4, 04/27/1949; wsyr_radio_003; opening of the Thompson Road Campus Science and Engineering - College of Applied Science; Lacquer discs/acetates
    Side 1: "Charles Kettering", Part II; Side 2: "Charles Kettering", Part IV
  - Christmas Eve in Syracuse, 12/24/1976; includes script; wsyr_radio_472; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 45:41 (Box 13)
  - Christmas Message, Bishop Ned Cole (1), 12/21/1970; wsyr_radio_860; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 4:12 (Box 47)
  - Christmas Piece, 12/24/1943; wsyr_radio_015; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 2)
    torn label, visible portion says "dman Christmas Piece, For WSYR, Part 1 of 1". A - Art Feldman, host interviews U. S. military members in London, England. Christmas message to Syracuse, N. Y. for WSYR
  - Christmas Special: Music from NORAD (North American Air Defense Command), wsyr_radio_929; note in box reads "Tommy Dorsey, original 78’s (left channel) only"; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 52)
  - Churchill - Fill before speech (part 1); Churchill (introduction by Major Churchill) (part 3), 11/09/1943; wsyr_radio_191; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Churchill at Waldorf Astoria (part 2), 03/15/1946; wsyr_radio_300; Side 2 is illegible; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Churchill at Waldorf Astoria, NBC, with Governor Dewey, Ambassador Winant (parts 1 and 3), 03/15/1946; wsyr_radio_299; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Citizen Report, No. 7, 04/20/1980; wsyr_radio_966; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 55)
  - Citizens for Bockman (Congressional election), wsyr_radio_592; note on box reads: "Bockman ad - Dub for station".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 22)
  - "Classics in recordings", 07/16/1947; wsyr_radio_433; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - "Classics in recordings" - Porgy and Bass, wsyr_radio_432; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Col Charles A. Lindbergh - "Why we should stay out of WW2?", 10/13/1939; wsyr_radio_134; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Collector’s Corner (Reel 1), wsyr_radio_442; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 59:18 (Box 9)
  - Collector’s Corner (Reel 2), wsyr_radio_443; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 65:23 (Box 9)
  - Collector’s Corner (Reel 3), wsyr_radio_444; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 64:21 (Box 9)
  - Collector’s Corner (Reel 4), wsyr_radio_445; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 64:21 (Box 9)
  - Collector’s Corner (Reel 5), wsyr_radio_446; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 48:21 (Box 9)
  - Collican LeMon Incorporated: Natur-Tyme Discount Vitamin Land, 05/05/1983; wsyr_radio_1032; 60-second recording, includes commercial scripts in box; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 0:60 (Box 59)
  - Colonel [LeGRande A.] Diller, Australia; President Roosevelt presenting Destroyer to French Navy, 12/22/1943; 02/12/1944; wsyr_radio_189; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Colonel L. A. Diller, Australia; "Here’s to youth" (part 2), 12/21/1943; 01/15/1944; wsyr_radio_190; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Command performance (part 2); R. C. A. Show - Music America Loves Best (part 2), 08/26/1945; 09/02/1945; wsyr_radio_272; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Command Performance, part 1, 09/02/1945; wsyr_radio_057; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 10)
    Armed Forces Radio Service Broadcast: "Command Performance". Heard: Invocation by Brigadier General Luther D. Miller, Chief of Chaplains, U. S. Army, Bing Crosby, Dinah Shore sings with chorus and orchestra "America", Bill Mauldin, Bob Hope, Ernie Pyle piece, Frank Sinatra "The house I live in", Dinah Shore sings "I've been walking on the railroad" with chorus: "Someone's in the kitchen", with Dinah (medley), Francis Langford sings "Don't sit under the apple tree". Side-B blank
  - Congressional Medal of Honor General [Jonathan Mayhew] Wainwright (part 2); Kiwanis Club - General Wainwright (part 2), 09/19/1945; 09/25/1945; wsyr_radio_278; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [Congressional Medal of Honor] General Wainwright (part 1); Kiwanis Club - General Wainwright (part 1), 09/19/1945; 09/25/1945; wsyr_radio_277; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Conversations From Wingspread, Program R-546: Learning a Trade or Vocational Education, 09/02/1979; wsyr_radio_937; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:21 (Box 53)
  - Conversations From Wingspread, Program R-547: Community Based Education; Police and Police Practices, 04/08/1979; wsyr_radio_936; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:10 (Box 53)
  - Conversations From Wingspread, Program R-558: White Collar Crime, 09/09/1979; wsyr_radio_938; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:18 (Box 53)
  - Conversations From Wingspread, Program R-589: Egypt and Israel, 06/17/1979; wsyr_radio_939; includes opening and closing scripts in box; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:35 (Box 53)
  - Conversations From Wingspread, Program R-599: Neighborhood Disputes, 11/04/1979; wsyr_radio_940; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:16 (Box 53)
  - Conversations From Wingspread, Program R-615: The Future for Taiwan, 12/30/1979; wsyr_radio_941; includes opening and closing scripts in box; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:18 (Box 53)
  - Conversations From Wingspread, Program R-641: Soviet Politics and Leadership, 12/23/1979; wsyr_radio_942; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:05 (Box 53)
  - Conversations From Wingspread, Program R-843: "Trade with China", 03/14/1982; wsyr_radio_574; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 28:25 (Box 21)
  - Cooperative Extension, New York State; President Ford Press Conference, 09/06/1972; 03/06/1975; wsyr_radio_997; note on label reads: "This tape is duplicated backwards - please expect a segment of blank tape at the beginning. Return immediately after broadcast, using the enclosed, postage-free mailing label. New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences, New York State College of Human Ecology, and United States Department of Agriculture"; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 57)
  - Cooperative Extention [sic], wsyr_radio_608; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 24)
  - Corporal Hickox interview with Bill Rothrum and Bob Nelson, parts 1 and 2, 05/14/1953; wsyr_radio_104; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 16)
  - "D - Day"(part 2); Special eye witness story (part 2), 06/06/1944; wsyr_radio_224; Lacquer discs/acetates
    #1 Eisenhower; W2 Chaplin; #4 Official invasion Announcement; #6 English Gen. Montgomery (incomplete); #7 Eye witness - landing
  - Dave Cohen Audition, wsyr_radio_593; note on box reads: "Please return if possible. Dave Cohen, 501A Sure Ave. Brooklyn, NY, 11224; 212-373-3669".; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 22)
  - "Day before War" (War Crisis News), # 1, 08/31/1939; wsyr_radio_117; Lacquer discs/acetates
    Labeled side: NBC Broadcast "Overseas news", Blue and Red network Feed: 1 - London; 2 - Paris. Complete, ends with chimes, 12-12:15. Side without label - starts with speech in French by a "Mr. (?) Whistler ands with further speech in French with translation."
  - Deacon [ Robert F.] Doubleday Tribute - COPY, 02/27/1971; wsyr_radio_468; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 120:00 (Box 13)
  - Deacon [Robert F.] Doubleday Memorial, Feb 24, 1971; wsyr_radio_487; broadcast on WSYR-AM-FM, 5AM-7AM and again 8:00-10:00 PM; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 120:00 (Box 15)
  - Deacon Doubleday Comes Down City (3 Shows), 1959; 1966; wsyr_radio_463; #1, 1966, #2 and 3, 1959; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 12)
  - Dean Acheson Report on Foreign Ministers conference and NATO; [unknown], 02/29/1952; wsyr_radio_398; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Decorating For You C, wsyr_radio_1020; box lists playback dates, recorded dates, running time and engineer’s initials; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 59)
    Dates are 10/04; 10/14; 10/18; 10/28; 11/01; 11/04; 11/15; 11/18; 11/29; 12/09; 12/13; 12/23; 12/03; 01/13. No year is given.
  - Dedication of Newhouse II, 05/31/1974; wsyr_radio_506; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 60:00 (Box 16)
    Formal dedication of Newhouse II at S.U. 10:30-11:30 AM, Friday, May 31, 1974. William Paley (CBS) - main speaker.
  - Dedication of St. Paul’s Cathedral in Syracuse, NY, wsyr_radio_603; includes transcription of recording inside box; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 23)
  - Delinquency, Carol Johnson, Art Willis, wsyr_radio_960; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 55)
  - Democratic View of The State of The Union (recorded off NBC; 10:00-10:50) (tape 2), 02/01/1974; wsyr_radio_991; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 50:00 (Box 57)
  - Dennis Dowdell - Rotary speech, wsyr_radio_610; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 24)
  - Documentary: Something Old, Something New, wsyr_radio_967; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 55)
  - Don Daver Aircheck - Morning farm show, Oct 24 [no year]; wsyr_radio_609; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 24)
  - "Double or nothing"; Wendell Willkie (part 1), 02/12/1941; 02/16/1941; wsyr_radio_154; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Dr. Allix B. James Address to United Negro College Fund Kick Off Luncheon, 04/21/1971; 04/22/1971; wsyr_radio_955; includes opening, closing, synopsis and newspaper clipping in box; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 18:15 (Box 55)
  - Dr. Calvin Thompson interviewing Indian Jesuit Priest, wsyr_radio_1023; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 20:00 (Box 59)
  - Dr. Charles Willie (1), 03/23/1971; 03/26/1971; wsyr_radio_953; includes opening and closing scripts in box; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 26:00 (Box 54)
  - Dr. Charles Willie (2), 03/23/1971; 03/26/1971; wsyr_radio_954; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 46:00 (Box 54)
  - Dr. Thompson Lunch (for broadcast 10:05 PM), 11/30/1964; wsyr_radio_951; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 42:20 (Box 54)
  - Dr. Whitney Young, wsyr_radio_959; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 55)
  - Dunk and Bright, Six hours Sale, wsyr_radio_1012; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 58)
  - Dwight D Eisenhower NATO Speech, 12/15/1957; wsyr_radio_034; UNPLAYABLE. NOT TRANSFERRED; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 6)
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower - Address to NATO, [Alan] Miliar; NATO Report by John Foster Dulles, parts 1 and 2, 05/24/1955; wsyr_radio_041; SIDE B UNPLAYABLE. NOT TRANSFERRED; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 7)
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower Speech (2nd Term) and talk, 02/29/1956; wsyr_radio_036; SIDE B UNPLAYABLE. NOT TRANSFERRED; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 7)
    Post heart attack activities
  - [Dwight D] Eisenhower - Address to United Nations 10 year Anniversary, [Alan] Milair, 06/30/1955; wsyr_radio_040; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 7)
  - Dwight Eisenhower from Denver (part 1), 06/23/1952; wsyr_radio_407; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - E. R. Vadeboncoeur Christmas Show [splice-free], 1966-1974; Christmas Day special, Dec 25 each year; wsyr_radio_1017; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 14:27 (Box 59)
  - E. R. Vadeboncoeur Christmas Tape (edited), Dec 1966; theme of program is the story of the birth of Jesus; program closes with Silent Night; wsyr_radio_1016; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 59)
  - E. R. Vadeboncoeur interprets the news - wartime stories (WSYR program); Premier [Édouard] Daladier from France, part 1, 09/23/1939; 10/10/1939; wsyr_radio_013; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 1)
  - E. R. Vadeboncoeur speech to Lions Club, wsyr_radio_080; Achievement Award, Buzz Record, President Merrit; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 17)
  - [Edouard] Daladier and Parker (part 1); NBC News bulletins, wsyr_radio_125; Lacquer discs/acetates
    Side 1 - NBC broadcast from Paris via short wave,, Daladier speech, A P. News continued, piano music incomplete, Paris Mondial, (1938/39 approx). Side 2 - Inside out: WW2 era, State at War between France and Germany mentioned. 1 An address by Premier of France Edouard Daladier in French with English translation. Germany invades France, broadcast from the short wave by NBC. Ends with news report - general France quotation. Open 2 - Short cut - News in Brief, sponsored by ESSO markerus by the ESSO reporter. Close 3 - short cut - ESSO commercial
  - Edwin Newman, Paul Ennis News (excerpt), 06/05/1972; wsyr_radio_1014; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 58)
  - Eisenhower and Nixon Inauguration, parts 1 and 2, Jan 1953; wsyr_radio_088; UNPLAYABLE. NOT TRANSFERRED; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 13)
  - Eisenhower Program from London (parts 1 and 3), 06/12/1945; wsyr_radio_243; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Eisenhower Program from London (parts 2 and 4), 06/12/1945; wsyr_radio_244; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Eisenhower speech (parts 1 and 2), 06/04/1952; wsyr_radio_404; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Eisenhower Victory Speech; Stevenson Admits Defeat, 11/01/1952; wsyr_radio_043; SIDE B UNPLAYABLE. NOT TRANSFERRED; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 17)
    A-President Elect Eisenhower Victory speech, Hotel Commodore; B-Governor Adlai Stevenson Concession speech
  - Eisenhower: 1953 State of Union Message, parts 1 and 3, 01/07/1954; wsyr_radio_086; UNPLAYABLE. NOT TRANSFERRED; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 13)
  - Eisenhower: 1953 State of Union Message, parts 2 and 4, 01/07/1954; wsyr_radio_087; note on label reads: "Start on Apr. 12th, 1945, end - That war my 1st [?]" UNPLAYABLE. NOT TRANSFERRED; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 13)
  - Electronic Music by Ken Grant - Untitled, 04/14/1967; wsyr_radio_1011; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 58)
  - Electronic music from "Nonesuch", wsyr_radio_600; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 23)
  - Elmer Denis - O. W. I.; West Point Anniversary Program (part 1), 03/12/1943; 03/13/1943; wsyr_radio_207; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Ernie Davis Hall of Fame Dinner conclusion [empty box], 10/19/1979; wsyr_radio_556; broadcast on WSYR-AM, 8:30pm; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 20)
  - Escape Drive Time audition, wsyr_radio_594; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 23)
  - Escape General demo, wsyr_radio_595; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 23)
  - European Crisis; Midway (Bill Rothbaum at NYS Fair), 08/28/1939; wsyr_radio_119; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - European reaction to Hitler speech; WSYR Intros - Outtros ESSO, 10/06/1939; wsyr_radio_132; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Fashion Show Music; Strings, 03/10/1959; wsyr_radio_033; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 6)
  - Fiftieth Anniversary of WSYR Show (segments) (1), 09/11/1972; 09/18/1972; wsyr_radio_969; master work tape (dub of individual parts of segments); 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 56)
    1: IKE - Complete segment (3:22); 2: Elliot Gove (0:42); 3: Dr. Calvin Thompson (0:28); 4: RF Deacon (0:45); 5: Jim Deline (1:14); 6: NBC News voice montage (0:19); 7: Windsor Castle (0:57); 8: Wendell Hall; 9: Hindenburg (0:56); 10: Pearl Harbor/ Roosevelt (0:37); 11: Eisenhower/ Truman (0:31); 12: Rothrum (1:39); 13: Commercial Sequence (0:43); 14: Murphy (1:25); 15: Hillega (Dedication) (1:20); 16: Curly, No.1 (0:38); 17: Curly (Fortyith) (1:08); 18: Maurice Chevallier (0:20); 19: Eddie Cantor (0:29); 20: Jimmy Durante (0:25); 21: C. McCarthy/ E. Bergan (0:33); 22: Fred Allen (1:00); 23: May West (0:27); 24: Alec Templeton (1:07); 25: J. Oakie/ D. Aneche (0:46); 26: Chas. Laughton (0:39); 27: NBC News Montage (long); 28: Curly (40-Ground Broak) (1:40); 29: Old Time Stars Montage (incomplete)
  - First broadcast from Tunis, 05/10/1943; wsyr_radio_020; NBC 5:15 PM (#5), John MacVane; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 2)
  - Food For Thought, Program 23 & 24, wsyr_radio_1019; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 59)
  - Francis X. O’Melia, 09/18/1955; wsyr_radio_037; SIDE B - UNPLAYABLE NOT TRANSFERRED; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 7)
    Side A - Union-VAW CIO Syracuse talk by Francis X. O'Melia [Melice?] Re: Voting in Union - New process gear
  - Fred Waring; President Roosevelt - Youth talk (part 2); Songs for a soldier (Ripley); Voice tracks, theme and bridges, 08/28/1942; 09/03/1942; wsyr_radio_180; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - French National Orchestra: Program 1: Rameau - Dutilleux (part 1), 04/04/1959; wsyr_radio_639; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 22:47 (Box 26)
    1 - Jean-Philippe Rameau (1683-1764): First Suite from Dardanus(13:32), The French National Orchestra, under the direction of Jean Martinon; 2 - Henri Dutilleux (1916-): Le Loup (The Wolf) - excerpt,(2:25), The Radio Symphony Orchestra of the FBS, under the direction of Eugene Bigot; 3 - Henri Dutilleux: Symphony (30:21), The French National Orchestra, under the direction of André Cluytens. Overall time: 53:29. Content list is in box.
  - From the Drums Onward (program 12), wsyr_radio_1029; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 10:27 (Box 59)
  - From the Drums Onward (program 4 & 5) (2:35 PM), 02/10/1976; wsyr_radio_1026; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 11:35 (Box 59)
    Program 4 - Cut 1, piano guitar (5:55); Program 5 - Cut 2 (5:40)
  - From the Drums Onward (program 6 & 7), wsyr_radio_1027; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 11:42 (Box 59)
    Program 6 - 5:30; Program 7 - 6:12
  - From the Drums Onward (program 8-11), wsyr_radio_1028; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 10:27 (Box 59)
    Program 8 - Jazz (2:33); Program 9 - The Harlem Sound (2;45); Program 10 - Cool Jazz (2:38); Program 11 - Back to the Roots (2:20)
  - From the Drums Onward, Black Music Bowles (Number 1), wsyr_radio_629; 8-Track cassette; running time 4:35 (Box 25)
  - From the Drums Onward, Girl Groups (Number 13), wsyr_radio_630; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 25)
  - From the Drums Onward, Johnny Cowber (program 1, 2 & 3), wsyr_radio_1025; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 6:52 (Box 59)
    Program 1, 0:32; Program 2, 3:50; Program 3, 2:30
  - General Clark Interview, part 1; H. R. Ekins, 07/16/1945; 07/07/1945; wsyr_radio_066; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 5)
    A - 1: Spot for WSYR program "Hiram's General Store" delivered by "Zekc"; 2: E. R. Vadeboncouer interviews Brigadier General Bruce Clark, Syracusan fro WSYR; B - H. R. Ekins, United Press Correspondent, WSYR Commentator, 6 PM Program
  - General Henri Giraud, wsyr_radio_209; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - General MacArthur speech to Congress (part 2); Groper, 04/19/1951; wsyr_radio_381; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - General MacArthur speech to Senate and House of Representatives, part 1; General MacArthur Keynote speech at GOP Convention, part 3, 04/18/1951; wsyr_radio_050; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 9)
  - General MacArthur; R. C. A. Show - Music America loves best, Dorsey, Monroe (part 2), 10/07/1945; 10/15/1945; wsyr_radio_286; Lacquer discs/acetates
    B - RCA Show, Tommy Dorsey, Vaughn Monroe, spot for RCA Steven foster album M 354 Vaughn Monroe sings"Racing with the Moon", Tommy Dorsey plays: "I’m getting sentimental over you"
  - General Ridgeway address to Joint session of Congress (parts 1 and 2), 05/22/1952; wsyr_radio_403; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - General Smutz address to Parliament, parts 2 and 4; Winston Churchill speaks, 1939; wsyr_radio_012; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 2)
  - General Wainwright - short interview; V-J Day Program - M. Bernthal, 08/13/1945; 09/08/1945; wsyr_radio_273; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - General Wainwright speaks at New York City Hall, 09/13/1945; wsyr_radio_276; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - General Wainwright’s arrival in San Francisco, 09/08/1945; wsyr_radio_274; one side doesn’t have label; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [General] MacArthur keynote speech at Republican convention, parts 1 and 3, 07/07/1952; wsyr_radio_045; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 8)
    A-1 Test cut, part of the broadcast; A-2 [General] MacArthur keynote speech at Republican convention (part 1); B-1: (part 3).
  - [General] MacArthur keynote speech at Republican convention, parts 2 and 4, 07/07/1952; wsyr_radio_046; dubbed from tape; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 8)
  - Generals Patton and Doolittle reception (part 2); Rome air show, 05/16/1945; 06/09/1945; wsyr_radio_246; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Generals Patton and Doolittle reception (part 4); Eisenhower -Pentagon building and Speech to Congress, 06/09/1945; 06/18/1945; wsyr_radio_247; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Generals Patton and Doolittle reception (parts 1 and 3), 06/09/1945; wsyr_radio_245; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - George Roberts Show - (part 3), 01/13/1974; wsyr_radio_501; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 25:00 (Box 16)
  - George Roberts Show 2/23/74 (part 3, number 4), 02/23/1974; wsyr_radio_504; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 25:00 (Box 16)
  - "Get out and vote", Syracuse Jaycees, Bill Purdy, President, wsyr_radio_631; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 25)
  - Gordon Foster - Hillegas Chief [Kiuncy] interview (Historical File), 06/16/1948; wsyr_radio_350; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Gospel Caravan, 06/26/1977; wsyr_radio_894; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 50)
  - Gospel Sound (11:05-11:30 AM Sunday), 03/04/1973; 03/11/1973; 03/18/1973; 04/01/1973; 04/08/1973; 04/14/0000; 04/28/0000; 05/05/0000; 05/13/0000; wsyr_radio_893; box lists multiple playback dates; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 25:00 (Box 49)
  - Governor Dewey - speech at opening of Thruway, 07/11/1946; wsyr_radio_322; Side 2 is illegible.; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Governor Dewey address to State Senate and Assembly (part 1), 01/07/1948; wsyr_radio_344; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Governor Dewey address to State Senate and Assembly (parts 2 and 4), 01/07/1948; wsyr_radio_345; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Governor Dewey radio speech, 09/07/1954; wsyr_radio_098; on his successor and announcing his retirement from public office; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 15)
  - Governor Rockefeller Addressing Greater Syracuse Chamber of Commerce, Intro by E. R. Vadeboncouer, 10/28/1971; wsyr_radio_965; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 55)
  - Governor Tom Dewey opens Thruway, Thompson Road Interchange (part 1 and 2), 06/24/1954; wsyr_radio_422; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - H. R. E. King Departure, 04/18/1946; wsyr_radio_301; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Hall of Fame of the Trotter: 8 Featurettes with Phil Pines, wsyr_radio_635; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 25)
  - Harness Racing with Phil Pines, wsyr_radio_611; scripts of "The introductions to The Great American Pastime" program are inside box; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 24)
  - Harry S. Truman Speech, parts 1 and 2, 11/16/1953; wsyr_radio_090; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 14)
    Attack on Former President Truman’s integrity; knowingly betraying the Security of the United States; Herbert Brownell, Jr., Attorney General Radio address to the American People. Side B - UNPLAYABLE
  - Health Information Foundation presents Raymond Massey in The Endless Frontier - "PFC Bill Smith - man alive" (part 1) and "Our daily bread" (part 2), wsyr_radio_386; Syndicated programs, 4 Rockhill transcriptions, 1948-1952; VinylDisc
  - Health Information Foundation presents Raymond Massey in The Endless Frontier: "The Search" (part 2) and "Our Daily Bread" (part 1), wsyr_radio_388; VinylDisc
  - Health Information Foundation presents Raymond Massey in The Endless Frontier: "PFC Bill Smith - Man Alive" (part 2) and "The Aearch", Part 1, wsyr_radio_387; VinylDisc
  - Health Information Foundation presents Raymond Massey in The Endless Frontier: "The trouble shooters" (part 1) and "Only one to a customer" (part 1), 7/12/52; wsyr_radio_389; VinylDisc
  - Health Information Foundation presents Raymond Massey in The Endless Frontier: "The trouble shooters" (part 2) and "Only one to a customer" (part 2), 07/12/1952; wsyr_radio_390; VinylDisc
  - Help from Virginia Knauer, Special Assistant to the President and Director, U. S. Office of Consumer Affairs, wsyr_radio_616; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 24)